Guide to the Collected editions of standard authors, ca. 1829-1903.
Collected editions of standard authors
- Irving, Washington; Mahomet Vol. II; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 25)
- Irving, Washington; The Alhambra; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 25)
- Irving, Washington; Tales of a Traveller; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1868 (Box 25)
- Irving, Washington; Salmagundi; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 25)
- Irving, Washington; Bracebridge Hall; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1867 (Box 25)
- Irving, Pierre M.; The Life and Letters of Washington Irving Vol. I;; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 25)
- Irving, Pierre M.; The Life and Letters of Washington Irving Vol. III;; G.P. Putnam and Son; New York; 1869 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Laughing Man Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Laughing Man Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Laughing Man Vol. III; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Laughing Man Vol. IV; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Toilers of the Sea Vol. I; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Toilers of the Sea Vol. II; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Toilers of the Sea Vol. III; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; The Toilers of the Sea Vol. IV; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Notre-Dame of Paris Vol. I; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Notre-Dame of Paris Vol. II; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Notre-Dame of Paris Vol. III; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Notre-Dame of Paris Vol. IV; George Barrie & Son; Philadelphia; 1892 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Ninety-Three Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Ninety-Nine Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Last Day of a Condemned Claude Guex; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Bug-Jargal; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Han of Iceland Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Han of Iceland Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1894 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables I: Fantine Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables I: Fantine Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables II: Cosette Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables II: Cosette Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables III: Marius Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables III: Marius Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables IV: Plumet and St. Denis Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables IV: Plumet and St. Denis Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables V: Jean Valjean Vol. I; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)
- Hugo, Victor; Les Miserables V: Jean Valjean Vol. II; George Barrie; Philadelphia; 1893 (Box 25)